- Hörrni.
- Mm?
What do your rooms look like?
Quite clean.
Ehm ... mine is not cleaned at all.
Okay.
I think it's time for us to make a jerk.
A cleaner.
- Oh no.
- No, it's so boring.
Yes, but then we can start the day ago, for real.
Okay then.
Have you talked anything about Alma's braids?
So, the viewers have not seen.
Now I'm going to go home to a classmate who will have a birthday party.
- And I'll just follow you there.
- Yes exactly.
You should not be allowed to come in.
- No no.
And neither do you.
- No, neither do you.
This one ... I thought I would carry the camera in it when we were not filming.
Now it is completely empty and just lumpy.
Flying around.
- Yes, but it is cleaned at home and Alma is going to be at a party.
- Yes.
"Yes!"
Lovely Sunday!
What kind of gift do you have?
I have this ... little bag.
I had no nice bag, so ...
- You made one.
- It's a little worn.
- Yes, but you drew a little nice on it.
- Yes.
I bought some necessity in necessity.
- Several necessities.
- Yes.
In nice color.
Oh.
And ... God, sorry.
And a bath bomb.
"Yes!"
- Oh, should they jump?
Do you think they dare?
- Yes.
Do you think so?
Oh, what a brave!
Laura goes through a very emotional period in her life right now.
She should stop with a diaper and she will end up with a pacifier, and she wants to dress all herself.
- She wants to do everything herself.
- Yes.
Oh, what do you want?
A banana?
Or apple?
Yes, you can take the apple.
And is it that you try to help her,-
- I think it will go great, Harry.
- Mm, may hope.
Come on we can collect some more flowers down there by the meadow.
Okay.
Here it was most green, not so much flowers.
- Yes, a small flower.
- It was small.
Unlucky.
Where are you going now, then?
Away there.
I'm going to take one of those flowers, because I'm really not sure if you can take away.
If you had been able to choose, would the family lived here in Lisbon then?
Easy.
Yes.